gawaksha.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Gawaksha IT Research Firm

_**Our mission is to connect buyers and sellers of IT services. To achieve this, we need to display some of the information of service providers for marketing point of view.**_

We protect your personal information and will only display to our website. We have appropriate security safeguards to protect your information in accordance with industry standards.

Kindly notice that our we make appropriate changes to our Privacy Policy time to time whenever we make significant changes to it. We will notify you for the same and you may review the changes we have made before agreeing upon the agreement and continuing with us. If you feel any kind of discomfort through these kinds of changes, you can contact us and discontinue your association with us.

You are consenting to the changes and our policies if you are continuing with Gawaksha.

### Information We Collect

If you have any concern about providing information to us or having such information displayed on the Gawaksha services or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you should not use the Website or register on Gawaksha. If you have already registered, you should close your account.

We collect your publicly displayed information in our research process. When you create an account with us, you provide us with personal information (including your name and email address) either directly or via your LinkedIn account. You need to understand that, by creating an account, Gawaksha and others will be able to identify you by your user profile, and you allow our website – Gawaksha to use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Agreement. You any need to fill your credit card details whenever you purchase any kind of paid subscription or services from Gawaksha.

You may also share personal information of other individuals (e.g. clients) such as name, email, phone number and company to support our reference check and review process.

We use cookies and similar technologies to help us recognize you, improve your Gawaksha experience, increase security, and measure use of our Services. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. By visiting our website, you consent to the placement of cookies and beacons in your browser in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We do not share personally identifiable information with any third-party advertiser or ad network, although your user profile is visible to other Gawaksha users and may be visible through public search. Additionally, Gawaksha currently does not share any personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

Please feel free to contact us on email if you have any kind of question or concern regarding your personal information or security.

**Contact Us –[info@gawaksha.com](mailto:info@gawaksha.com)**
